{
  "task": [
    {
      "question": " What was the name of Abraham's son born to Sarah?",
      "time": "8000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Jacob"
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Ishmael"
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. Isaac"
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Abimelech"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "c. Isaac",
      "type": "epi_10"
    },
    {
      "question": " Where did Hagar and Ishmael wander after they left Abraham? ",
      "time": "12000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. The hill country of Hebron "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. The desert of Arabia "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c.  The region by the Salt Sea "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d.  The wilderness of Beersheba "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "d. The wilderness of Beersheba ",
      "type": "epi_10"
    },
    {
      "question": " When God opened the eyes of Hagar what did she see?  ",
      "time": "10000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a.  A fountain "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b.  A stream "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c.  An oasis "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. A well "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "d. A well ",
      "type": "epi_10"
    },
    {
      "question": " When did Abraham circumcise his son?    ",
      "time": "8000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. The twelfth day "
        },
        {
          "choice": " b. The third day "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c.  The seventh day "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. The eighth day "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "d. The eighth day ",
      "type": "epi_10"
    },
    {
      "question": " Who made a treaty with Abraham and received seven lambs? ",
      "time": "11000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Abimelech and Phicol "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Melchizedek and Abimelech "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. Lot and Melchizedek "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Og and Sihon "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "a. Abimelech and Phicol",
      "type": "epi_10"
    },
    {
      "question": " How old was Abraham when his son by Sarah was born? ",
      "time": "8000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. 75 "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. 110 "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. 90 "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. 100 "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "d. 100 ",
      "type": "epi_10"
    },
    {
      "question": " Where did Hagar put Ishmael when she thought he was going to die? ",
      "time": "12000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Under some bushes "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Under the shade of a rock "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c.  Beside an altar "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. In the gateway of a city "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "a. Under some bushes ",
      "type": "epi_10"
    },
    {
      "question": " What was Sarah's response to Ishmael's the mocking of her son?",
      "time": "15000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. She told Abraham to get rid of Hagar and Ishmael "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. She told Abraham that Hagar and Ishmael should be killed "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c.  She told Abraham that Hagar and Ishmael should be sold as slaves "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d.  She told Abraham he should do what is right in his eyes with Ishmael and Hagar "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "a. She told Abraham to get rid of Hagar and Ishmael",
      "type": "epi_10"
    },
    {
      "question": " What did the response of those who hear about Sarah having a son?  ",
      "time": "8000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Joy "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Laughter "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c.  Strength "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Praise "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "b. Laughter ",
      "type": "epi_10"
    },
    {
      "question": " What promise did God make to both Abraham and Hagar concerning Ishmael?  ",
      "time": "12000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. He would become a nation "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. He would be an adversary to all his brothers "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. He would be blessed "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. He would live in the desert "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "a. He would become a nation ",
      "type": "epi_10"
    }
  ]
}


